Guide to the Veterinary Reprint and Pamphlet Collection, 1865-1950
Veterinary Reprint and Pamphlet Collection, 1865-1950
- M
  - _______. Pasteurization of Skim Milk and Whey as Food for Calves [ read at New York State Agricultural Society meeting, 18-19 January 1916. New York Commission for the Investigation of Bovine Tuberculosis, 1916. (Box 3)
  - _______. Poultry Diseases, Especially Bacillary White Diarrhea and Tuberculosis [read at Farmers' Institute for State Institution Farm Workers meeting, 15-17 December 1926]. Agricultural Bulletin, December 1926. (Box 3)
  - _______. Portraits of Distinguished Verinarians Presented to Saddle and Sirloin Club. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, January 1919. (Box 3)
  - _______. Powdered Soap as the Cuase of Death Among Swill-Fed Hogs. Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station Bulletin, November 1897. (Box 3)
  - _______. Preliminary Observations on Skin Disinfection and Wound Infection. American Veterinary Review, October 1901. (Box 3)
  - _______. Preparation of Tuberculin, Its Value as a Diagnositc Agent, and Remarks on the Human and Bovine Tubercle Bacilli. Albany Medical Annals, 1900. (Box 3)
  - _______. Preparation of Tuberculin, Its Value as a Diagnositc Agent, and Remarks on the Human and Bovine Tubercle Bacilli. Transactions of the Medical Society of the State of New York, 1900. (Box 3)
  - _______. President's Address to the Cornell Chapter of the Society of the Sigma Xi. 6 June 1903. (Box 3)
  - _______. Problem of Tuberculosis in Cattle. Cornell Reading Course for the Farm, Livestock Series, June 1919. (Box 3)
  - _______. Progress in Veterinary Education. Cornell Veterinarian. (Box 3)
  - _______. Protection of Domesticated Animals. Popular Science Monthly, December 1913. (Box 3)
  - _______. Questions in Bacteriology. (Box 3)
  - _______. Questions on Meat Inspection, ca. 1900. (Box 3)
  - _______. Rabies and its Control. Proceedings of the United States Live Stock Association, 1924. (Box 3)
  - _______. Rabies and its Control. New York State Journal of Medicine, 15 August 1927. (Box 3)
  - _______. Rabies in New York State. New York State Journal of Medicine, February 1909. (Box 3)
  - _______. Rapid Method for the Diagnosis of Rabies. American Veterinary Review, October 1904. (Box 3)
  - _______. Relation of Animal Experimentation to the Live Stock Industry. Committee on Experimental Medicine of the Medical Society of the State of New York, 1909. (Box 3)
  - _______. Relation of Human and Bovine Tuberculosis. Cornell Countryman, April 1904. (Box 3)
  - _______. Relation of Undulant Fever in Man to Live Stock Sanitation [read at United States Live Stock Sanitary association meenting, Chicago, 5-7 December 1928]. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, March 1929. (Box 3)
  - _______. Remarks on Anthrax and Rabies with Special Reference to Outbreaks Recently Investigated. Annual Report of the Commissioner of Agriculture of New York State, 1897? (Box 3)
  - _______. Remarks on the Nature and Differntiation of the Infectious Swine Diseases in the United States. American Veterinary Review, March 1898. (Box 3)
  - _______. Report on Bovine Tuberculosis. New York Department of Agriculture, 1903. (Box 3)
  - _______. Report Concerning the Nature of Infections Swine Diseases in the State of New York, with Practical suggestions for their Prevention and Treatment. Annual Report of the Commissioner of Agriculture of New York State, 1897. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ the Commission. Report of the Commission for the Investigation of Bovine Tuberculosis. New York State Commission for the Investigation of Bovine Tuberculosis, March 1915. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ the Committee. Report of Committee on Poultry Diseases of the United States Live Stock Sanitary Association. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, March 1927. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ the Committee. Report of Committee on Standard Methods for the Diagnosis of Rabies. Journal of the American Public Health Association, June 1911. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ the Committee. Report of the Committee on Standard Methods for the Preparation of Tuberculin and Mallein. American Journal of Public Hygiene, August 1910. (Box 3)
  - _______. Report of the Dean of the New York State Veterinary College, 1914. (Box 3)
  - _______. Report of the Dean of the New York State Veterinary College, 1918. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ the Commission. Report of the International Commission on the Control of Bovine Tuberculosis. Annual Report of the American Veterinary Medical Association, 1910. (Box 3)
  - _______w/ G. Franklin White. Report on the Investigation of an Infectious Bee Disease. New York Department of Agriculture, 1903. (Box 3)
  - _______. Report to Forest, Fish and Game Commission Relative to Diseases of Deer. New York Forest, Fish and Game Commission Bulletin, 1905. (Box 3)
  - _______. Reports of Drs. Veranus A. Moore, Mazyck, P. Ravenel, and William T. Sedgwick upon Federal Meat Inspection. United States Department of Agriculture Circular, May 1916. (Box 3)
  - _______. Report on Rabies in Washington, D.C. Report of the Bureau of Animal Industry, 1896?. (Box 3)
  - _______. Review of the Methods of Demonstrating the Flagella on Motile bacteria with Special Reference to the Staining Processes [read at Washington Microscopial Society meeting, 20 February1891]. American Monthly Microscopial Journal, January 1891. (Box 3)
  - _______. Significance of Crises in the Veterinary Profession. Cornell Veterinarian, October 1925. (Box 3)
  - _______. Some Methods Employed in Northern Europe to Control Bovine Tuberculosis, 1910. (Box 3)
  - _______. Some Principles of Pathology Significant in the Control of Animal Diseases, 1907. (Box 3)
  - _______. Some Problems for the Veterinarian. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, April 1925. (Box 3)
  - _______. Special Report to the President of Cornell University, 1908. (Box 3)
  - _______. State Law Relative to the Physical Examination of Cattle. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, October 1919. (Box 3)
  - _______. Status of Bovine Tuberculosis in New York State with Suggestions for Improving the Method for its Control: Together with a Copy of the Laws and a Summary of the Methods for its Control in Certain Other States, 1907. (Box 3)
  - _______. Study of Avian Tuberculosis. Zeitschrift fur Infektions-krankheiten, Parasitare Krankheiten und Hygiene der Haustiere, 1906. (Box 3)
  - _______. Study of Infectious Abortion in Cattle. Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College, 1913. (Box 3)
  - _______. Study of Infectious Abortion in Cattle. New York Department of Agriculture Bulletin, 1914. (Box 3)
  - _______. Suppurative Cellulitis in the Limbs of Cattle due to Streptococcus Infection. American Veterinary Review, June 1898. (Box 3)
  - _______. Technique And Value Of Sputum-Examination. Medical News, 14 May 1892. (Box 3)
  - _______. Thermo-regulated Waterbaths for the Bacteriological Laboratory. Journal of Applied Microscopy. (Box 4)
  - _______. Topics of Interest in the Control of Animal Diseases. Report of the Committe on Diseases of the American Veterinary Medical Association, 1913. (Box 4)
  - _______. Transmission of Diseases of Cattle to Man Through Milk. New York State Journal of Medicine, April 1919. (Box 4)
  - _______. Tuberculin and its Use in the Control of Bovine Tuberculosis. New York State Veterinary College Circular, August 1908. (Box 4)
  - _______. Undulant Fever. Cornell Veterinarian, April 1930. (Box 4)
  - _______. Undulant Fever. Extension Service News, February 1930. (Box 4)
  - _______ w/ Charles M. Carpenter. Undulant Fever in Man Associated with Bacteria Indistinguishable from Brucella Abortus. Cornell Veterinarian, April 1926. (Box 4)
  - _______. United States Government Meat Inspection. Report of the 17th Annual Meeting of the United States Live Stock Sanitary Association, December 1913, March 1914. (Box 4)
  - _______. Value of Tuberculin in the Control of Tuberculous Herds [read at International Congress on Tuberculosis, Washington, September 1908]. American Veterinary Review, January 1909. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinarian and Conservation. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, February 1918. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinarian and His Profession. Alumnus [Kansas City Veterinary College], April 1916. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinary Curriculum, Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association., December 1922. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinary Education. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, March 1923. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinary Education and Service at Cornell University. Cornell Veterinarian, April 1929. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinary Practitioner in the Control of Infectious Diseases. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, December 1917. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinary Profession: Its Requirements and Opportunities. Cornell Veterinarian, April 1914. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinary Science and its Problems. American Veterinary Review, June 1910. (Box 4)
  - _______. Veterinary Scienceas an Economic Factor. Cornell Veterinarian, January 1926. (Box 4)
  - _______. What General and What Specific Rules Should be Observed in Fixing the Periods and Duration of the Different Forms of Quarantine Against Foot-and-Mouth Disease. Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, January 1916. (Box 4)
  - _______ w/ Morris Wooden? Why Sterilized Milk Should be Used. (Box 4)
  - Moore, Willis L. "A Report on the influence of forests on climate and on floods." House of Representatives, United States Committee on Agriculture, 1910. (Box 4)
  - Mori, Nello. "Ancora sull'ipotesi della natura micetica dei virus filtrabili gli inframiceti e le inframicosi." Reprinted from Bollettino della Società Italiana di Biologia Sperimentale, Vol. XXVII, 1951. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Esperimenti di cura delcancro umano mediante l'isopatina anticancerigna." Reprinted from Riforma Medica, Anno XLII, n.7, February 1926. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Filtrierbare Vira und Krebs im Einklang mit meiner Hypothese über deren myzeliale Natur." Reprinted from Der Krebsarzt, 1949. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Isopatina neoplastica Mori: immunoterapia complementare dei trattamenti locali delle neoplasie." Instituto di Microbiologia. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Le Isopatine." Reprinted from Annali Italiai di Chirurgia, Anno VIII, 1929. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Le isopatine nelle applicazioni terapeutiche e profilattiche." Reprinted from Rivista Sanitaria, N.11, 1933. (Box 4)
  - ________. "L'isopatinoprofilassi del Barbone bufalino (setticemia emorragica dei bufali)." Reprinted from Profilassi - Rivista di Patologia Comparata, Anno VI, fasc. 6, Giugno 1933, XI. (Box 4)
  - ________. "L'isopatinoterapia del cancro." Reprinted from the Proceedings of the Secondo Convegno Nazionale, Bologna, 4-5 gennaio 1931. (Box 4)
  - ________. "L'isopatinoterapia nel farcino criptococcico degli equini." Reprinted from Profilassi - Rivista di Patologia Comparata, Anno VI, Fasc. 10, October 1933. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Il metodo isopatinico nella terapia del cancro." Reprinted from Atti Del Congresso internacional de lucha cientifica y social contra el cancer, 1933. (Box 4)
  - ________. "La mia ipotesi della natura micetica degli ultravirus." Reprinted from Atti del R. Istituto d'Incoraggiamento di Napoli, Anno 1930. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Il mio metodo di cura dei neoplasmi maligni, mediante l'isopatina antineoplastica, dopo 10 anni di esperimenti." Reprinted from Riforma Medica, Anno XLIII, n.42, 1927. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Il nucleo dei batteri secondo le mie ricerche citologiche del 1912-1913." Reprinted from Nuovi Annali d'Igiene e Microbiologia, Vol. V, n.5, 1953. (Box 4)
  - ________. "A proposito della mia concezione etiopatogenetica simbioparassitaria inframicetica del cancro." Reprinted from Atti de VII Congresso Nazionale della Lega Italiana per la lotta contro i tumori, Guigno 1953. (Box 4)
  - ________. "A proposito di una recente pubblicazione sull'etiologia dei tumori maligni." Reprinted from La Riforma Medica, n.38, 1937. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Sulla etiopatogenesi del cancro." Reprinted from Bollettino della Societa Italiana di Biologia Sperimentale, Vol.XXVII, 1951. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Sulla immunoterapia isopatinica del Farcino criptococcio degli equini." Reprinted from Il Progresso Veterinario, February 1949. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Sulla isopatinoterapia e sulla isopatinoprofilassi del cancro." Reprinted from Journées d'études biologiques du cancer, maggio 1933. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Virus filtrabili e cancro secondo la mia ipotesi (1914) della loro natura micetica." Reprinted from Il Progresso Medico, Vol.VI, N.12, 1950. (Box 4)
  - Morrison, H.B and F.E. Hull. "The presence of agglutinins for brucella abortus in milk." Kentucky Agricultural Experiment Station, University of Kentucky, Bulletin No.369, April 1937. (Box 4)
  - Morse, George Byron. "Quail disease in the United States." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Circular No. 109, 18 May 1907. (Box 4)
  - Motas, C.S. "Le role des protozoaires dans les maladies des animaux." VIII Congres International de medecine veterinaire Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Mugrage, E. R. "Diseases of animals communicable to man." Reprinted from Colorado Medicine, May 1927. (Box 4)
  - Muller, O. "Die milch-und molkereiprodukte als verbreiter der tuberkulose." VIII Internationaler Tierarztlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Murdoch, H.E. and Howard Welch. "Some stock ranch accessories." University of Montana, Agricultural Experiment Station, Cicular 84, February 1919. (Box 4)
  - Murphy, Francis D. and Gail F. Moxon. "Diabetes mellitus and its complications: an analysis of 827 cases." Reprinted from the American Journal of Medical Sciences, September 1931. (Box 4)
  - Musser, J. H. "The Essential of the Art of Medicine." Reprinted from The Journal of the American Medical Association, 25 June 1898. (Box 4)
  - Myers, Burton D. "The chisma of the toad (bufo lentiginosus) and of some other vertebrates." Zeitschrift fur morphologie und anthroplogie, 1901. (Box 4)
  - Myers, Victor. "Chemical analysis of blood in general and urologic surgery." Reprinted from The Journal of Laboratory and Clinical Medicine, May 1931. (Box 4)
- N
  - Nagler, F.P.O. and Geoffrey Rake. "The use of the electron microscope in diagnosis of variola, vaccinia, and varicella. " Reprinted from the Journal of Bacteriology, January 1948. (Box 4)
  - Nelson, Julius. "The suppression and prevention of tuberculosis of cattle and its relation to human consumption." New Jersey Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 118, 30 November 1896. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Report of the Biological Department of the New Jersey Agricultural Experiment Station for 1894." 1895. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Report of the Biological Department of the New Jersey Agricultural Experiment Station for 1895." 1896. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Report of the Biological Department of the New Jersey Agricultural Experiment Station for 1896." 1897. (Box 4)
  - Nocard. "Mortality among calves in Munster." Department of Agriculture and Technical Instruction for ireland, Bulletin No. 1, 1901. (Box 4)
  - Nörgaard, Victor A. "Blackleg: its nature, cause, and prevention." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Circular 31, 4 March 1911. (Box 4)
  - ________. "Blackleg in the United States and the distribution of vaccine by the Bureau of Animal Industry." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the Bureau of Animal Industry, 1898. (Box 4)
  - Novy, Frederick G. "Trypanosomes." Reprinted from the Journal of the American Medical Association, issues of January 5 and 12, 1907, Vol.XLVIII. (Box 4)
  - ________. "The trypanosomes of mosquitoes and other insects." Reprinted from The Journal of Infectious Diseases, Vol.4, No.2, April 1907 (Box 4)
  - ________. and R.E. Knapp "Studies in spirillum obermeieri and related organisms." Reprinted from the Journal of Infectious Diseases, Vol.III, No.3, May 1906. (Box 4)
- O
  - Ogden, Robert Morris. "The idea of the university." School and Society, 1919. (Box 4)
  - Ohlmacher, A.P. "laboratory instruction in elementary comparative anatomy and embryology." Reprinted from the New York Medical Journal, 6 January 1894. (Box 4)
  - Olson, Carl and Alexander Zeissig. "A study of the antigenic properties of certain normal and pathological lymphoid deposits in tissues of chickens." Reprinted from The Journal of Immunology, October 1936. (Box 4)
  - Olt, Giessen. "Der krebs der haustiere." Internationaler Tierarztlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
- P
  - Parker, Herman B., et al. "Report of working party no. 1, yellow fever institute: A study of the etiology of yellow fever." United States Treasury Department, Public Health and Marine-Hospital Service, Yellow Fever Institute Bulletin No. 13, 1903. (Box 4)
  - Parkinson, John and D. Evan Bedford. "The pulmonary artery impression on the a esophagus." Reprinted from Lancet, 15 August 1931. (Box 4)
  - Parlato, Salvatore J. "The sand fly (caddis fly) as an exciting cause of allergic coryza and asthma." Reprinted from The Journal of Allergy, May 1930. (Box 4)
  - Pearce, Richard M. "The scientific method in medicine." Reprinted from Albany Medical Annals, January 1905. (Box 4)
  - Pearson, Leonard. "The effect of tuberculosis vaccination upon cattle infected with tuberculosis." Reprinted from the University of Pennsylvania Medical Bulletin, April 1905. (Box 4)
  - ________ ."Tuberculosis of cattle." Pennsylvania State College Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 29, October 1894. (Box 4)
  - ________ and M.P. Ravenel. "Tuberculosis of cattle and the Pennsylvania plan." Commonweath of Pennsylvania Department of Agriculture, Bulletin No. 75, 1901. (Box 4)
  - Pearson, R.A. "Some influences in favor of better market milk." Reprinted from the Boston Medical and Surgical Journal, 26 April 1906. (Box 4)
  - Perroncito, E. "Vaccination contre la fievre aphteuse." Congres International de Medecine Veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - _________. "Les substances toxiques produite par des parasites animaux." Congres International de Medecine Veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Peterson, Elmer George. "The elimination of tubercle bacilli from man and animals." Reprinted from the Report of the New York State Veterinary College, 1909-1910. (Box 4)
  - Phillips, W.F.R. "Sunstroke weather of August, 1896." From the Monthly Weather Review, November 1896. Piot, J. B. "Maladies tropicales du betail observees en Egypt." VIII Congres International de Medecine Veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Piot, J. B. "Maladies tropicales du betail observees en Egypt." VIII Congres International de Medecine Veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Piratininga, Sebastiao Nicolau. "Contribuicao a semiologia 'tempo de circulacao' no cao." Sau Paolo, Brasil, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Porter, Eugene H. "What the state shall do in the care and supervision of school children." Issued by the New York State Department of Health Division of Publicity and Education, 25 August 1913. (Box 4)
  - Pottenger, F.M. "Tuberculosis of insidious onset and of acute onset." Reprinted from The Journal of the American Medical Association, 7 December 1929. (Box 4)
  - Preisz, H. "Sind die tuberkelbacillen des menschen, der saugetiere und der vogel artverschieden oder nicht?" Internationaler Tierarztlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - ______. "Die bakampfung der schweineseuche und schweinepest mit berucksichtigung der schutzimpfungen." Internationaler Tierarzlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Prescott, Samuel C. "The teaching of microbiology in colleges of United States and Canda." Reprinted from Science, 8 March 1912. (Box 4)
  - Price, W.A. "Recommendations for using DDT." University of Kentucky, College of Agriculture and Home Economics, Agricultural Extension Division, circular 438, 1947 (Box 4)
  - Pride, W.T. "Retraction ring dystocia." Reprinted from Surgery, Gynecology and Obstetrics, June 1938. (Box 4)
  - Profe, Konigl. "ausdehnung der verkehrsbeschrankungen beim auftretn der nicht unmittelbar contagiosen infectionskrankheiten, namentlich des milzbrandes." Internationaler Tierarztlicher Congress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Puckner, W.A. "The Council on Pharmacy and Chemistry, present and future." Reprinted from The Journal of the American Medical Association, 1919. (Box 4)
  - Pusch, D. "Hygiene des stalles und der streu; kritik der verschiedenen streuarten." Internationaler Tierarzlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
- R
  - Ranney, Albert F. "The elimination of brucella abortus from the feces of calves taking infected milk." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, July 1934. (Box 4)
  - Ransom, B.H. "The gid parasite (coenurus cerebralis): its presence in american sheep." U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Ravenel, Mazyck R. "Intercommunicability of human and bovine tuberculosis." Medicine, July/August 1902. (Box 4)
  - Ravenel, Mazyck R. "Intercommunicability of human and bovine tuberculosis: An address delivered at the annual conversational meeting of the Pathological Society of Philadelphia, on Thursday evening, April 24, 1902." Reprinted from the University of Pennsylvania Medical Bulletin, May 1902. (Box 4)
  - Redfield, Casper, L. "Human Heredity." April 1921. (Box 4)
  - Reed, Walter. "A comparative study of the biological characters and pathogenesis of bacillus x (Sternberg), bacillus icteroides (Sanarelli), and the hog-cholera bacilus (Salmon and Smith)." Reprinted from The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 15 December 1900. (Box 4)
  - __________and James Carroll. "The prevention of yellow fever." Reprinted from Medical Record, 26 October 1901. (Box 4)
  - __________and James Carroll. "The etiology of yellow fever." Reprinted from Philadelphia Medical Journal, 27 October 1900. (Box 4)
  - __________and James Carroll. "The specific cause of yellow fever.: A reply to Dr. G. Sanarelli." Reprinted from The Medical News, 9 September 1899. (Box 4)
  - Reynolds, M.H. "Bovine tuberculosis." University of Minnesota Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 51, December 1896. (Box 4)
  - Richardson, Garwood C. "The role of viosterol in pregnancy." Reprinted from the Illinois Medical Journal, June 1931. (Box 4)
  - Richardson, Mark Wyman. "The importance of animal experimentation in the devlopment of our knowledge of dysentery, cholera and typhoid fever." Defense of Research Pamphlet VIII, Issued by the Council on Defense of Medical Research of the American Medical Association, 1910. (Box 4)
  - Rickard, Charles G. "The opsonocytophagic test in bovine brucellosis." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, October 1945. (Box 4)
  - Ricqles, A.E. "Marketing live stock." A Statement made at a hearing held at Chicago, 15-16 November 1915. (Box 4)
  - Ridala, V. "Kaks teovoimsat munajuha kanal." Tartu, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Riegler, M.P. "La morve pulmonaire et les autres formations tuberculeuses pouvant etre confondues avec elle." Congres International de Medecine Veterinaire Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Rishoi, A.H. and Paul F. Sharp. "Specific heat and the physical state of the fat in cream." Reprinted from the Journal of Dairy Science, July 1938. (Box 4)
  - Rivers, T.M. "Viruses." Reprinted from The Journal of the American Association, 6 April 1929. (Box 4)
  - Rockl, Kaiserl. "Einheitliches muster fur die regelmassigen nachweisungen uber die verbreitung von tierseuchen." Internationaler Tierarzticher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 4)
  - Rogers, L.A. "Investigations on the manufacture and storage of butter." U.S. Department of Agriculture Bureau of Animal Industry, 1906. (Box 4)